{
  "category": "diy",	
  "sections": [
    {
      "title": "About",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "Developer",
          "question": "Developer",
          "answer": "Atari Monk  \n\n* [Games](https://atari-monk.itch.io/)  \n* [GitHub](https://github.com/atari-monk?tab=repositories)  ",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T13:13:15.687Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Art",
          "question": "Art",
          "answer": "\"You are a small incrustation on the atropic tides of the universe  \nand the meaning of our existence in some sense is to eat.  \nIt's very disheartening because it means that we are a type of yeast.  \nAll the amazing complexity that we create in our lives and the civilization, whatever,  \nis to create some surfaces on which we can outcompete other kinds of yeast.  \nAnd what we can do is we can do something else. We can serve a conspiracy.  \nFor instance, the arts. It's nicest conspiracy.  \nIt comes from a machine learning system falling in love  \nwith the shape of the modeling function itself.  \nIt's that you start thinking that mental representations are intrinsically important.  \nNow, the purpose of mental representation is to make you eat more, of course, right?  \nIt's a tool for learning, turning food into babies.  \nYes, right. But if you see that the beauty of this thing, and you realize,  \nOh my god, careing for conscious states, it's much more significant than to eat.  \nYou basically turn from an orc to an elf.  \nArt is some kind of truth that captures a certain conscious state, a feeling of what it's like.\"  \n\nJocha Bach  \n",
          "dateTime": "2024-02-13T15:55:03.021Z"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Games",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "ball_game_1",
          "question": "[ball_game_1](https://kind-moss-0f787ca03.3.azurestaticapps.net/)  ",
          "answer": "* This taught me, that server should contain game and synchronize clients\n* Here game code was on clients and server was synchronizing, witch turned out incalculable for me",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T13:19:12.050Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "ball_game_2",
          "question": "[ball_game_2](https://atari-monk.itch.io/ball-game-2)  ",
          "answer": "* 2 players ball game, pong style",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T13:20:22.055Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "ball_game_2.5",
          "question": "[ball_game_2.5](https://polite-bush-063bc3b03.3.azurestaticapps.net/)",
          "answer": "* Mobile multiplayer version\n* This taught me that engine provides organization and tools\n* Otherwise spaghetti code complexity",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T13:21:10.756Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "pong",
          "question": "[pong](https://atari-monk.github.io/js-pong-page/pong.html)  \n[pong project](https://atari-monk.github.io/js-pong-page/)",
          "answer": "* My pong\n* Two players with mouse and arrows on same pc",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T14:18:47.431Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "best_game_ever",
          "question": "[best_game_ever](https://atari-monk.itch.io/best-game-ever)  ",
          "answer": "* Done during this [TUTORIAL](https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLrnPJCHvNZuCVTz6lvhR81nnaf1a-b67U)",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T13:22:33.775Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "pokemon",
          "question": "[pokemon](https://atari-monk.github.io/pokemon-tutorial/)",
          "answer": "* Coded during [Tutorial](https://youtu.be/yP5DKzriqXA?feature=shared)\n* Go walk on grass to start fight",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T13:46:15.224Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "dog_game",
          "question": "[dog_game](https://atari-monk.github.io/js-game-beginner/)",
          "answer": "* Page Coded during [Tutorial](https://youtu.be/GFO_txvwK_c?feature=shared)\n* Js only ",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T14:01:41.778Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "arkanoid",
          "question": "[arkanoid](https://atari-monk.github.io/js-pong-page/arkanoid.html)",
          "answer": "* Classic done with [Tutorial](https://compucademy.net/html5-breakout-game/?utm_content=cmp-true)",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T14:33:35.149Z"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Apps",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "task_app",
          "question": "[task_app](https://red-beach-032340203.3.azurestaticapps.net/) ",
          "answer": "* Goodle Login service, Web api, MongoDb, React \n* Data on Project and Task model",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T13:28:16.686Z"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Pages",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "notes_2",
          "question": "[notes_2](https://atari-monk.github.io/atari-monk-notes/)",
          "answer": "* Second page with notes\n* Learned that api with md is simplest and best, witch later chatgtp page proved",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T13:24:49.331Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "notes_3",
          "question": "[notes_3](https://atari-monk.github.io/notes/note_page/build/index.html)",
          "answer": "* Static page with notes using json and md\n[Inventory](https://atari-monk.github.io/notes/inventory_page/build/index.html)",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T13:25:35.562Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "wood_stock_app",
          "question": "[wood_stock_app](https://green-beach-088189603.3.azurestaticapps.net/)",
          "answer": "* Simple react app, web api, mongodb\n* To collect wood stock data",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T13:32:19.430Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "socket_io_chat",
          "question": "[socket_io_chat](https://atari-monk.github.io/samples/socket-io-client/client.html)",
          "answer": "* Server and clinet for simple chat\n* Server wakes up minutes long",
          "dateTime": "2024-03-19T13:38:45.194Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "histogram",
          "question": "histogram",
          "answer": "[histogram 01/2024](https://atari-monk.github.io/notes/histogram/index.html)   ",
          "dateTime": "2024-02-13T16:24:03.777Z"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}